HELLO, TWENTY - WONHEE
ONE FINE DAY WITH DAZZLING SUNLIGHT
AND LUSH GREEN LEAVES
Hello, today,
I can't wait to see
what new experience is in store for me.
What's waiting for me
in this special place?
Can you guess where we are?
A Buddhist temple.
A TEMPLE?
Have you ever visited one?
I've always wanted to
whenever I had a lot on my mind,
so I had a few pinned on the map.
I've never actually visited one,
so I'm happy to be here.
I'll share today's theme.
People in their 20s are starting
to realize the importance of self-care.
Of course, that's very important.
YOU LEARN TO CARE FOR YOURSELF AT 20
YOUNG ADULTS IN THEIR 20S
NEED TIME TO FOCUS ON THEMSELVES
SIXTH ITEM ON WONHEE'S BUCKET LIST
TEMPLE STAY
Today is your chance to look inward
and care for both your mind and body.
TEMPLE STAY, FOCUSING ON MINDFULNESS
Why don't you call today's guest?
Girlie!
Wonhee!
- Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
You look so adorable.
EPISODE 6 GIRLIE
MIYEON OF I-DLE
Gosh, thank you.
SLIGHTLY AWKWARD
- We've never had a proper chat before.
- Right?
We've only said hello
when we were on the same music show.
- Right.
- "Hello."
Our interactions
- only lasted a fraction of a second.
- Honestly,
I see you on my social media all the time.
I already feel like we're friends.
I didn't know you turned 20 this year.
- Really?
- I thought you'd still be a teenager.
- I'm legal this year.
- Seriously?
No, don't be.
ASTOUNDED
I can't believe it.
We'd have to cancel this show, then.
STAY 20 FOREVER, WONHEE
- Hello.
HERE'S THEIR GUIDE
- It's nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
I guide participants in the temple stay
here at Seokbulsa Temple.
I'm Bhikshuni Yeomok.
- Bhikshuni Yeomok.
- That's right.
My Dharma name means "like trees."
During your temple stay program,
I'll be your tree to rest under.
Thank you.
We'll get started shortly.
Let's get changed
into temple stay uniforms.
- Yes.
- Of course.
Our cute outfits will barely get
any screen time.
Goodbye now.
One, two, three.
A LITTLE KEEPSAKE
BEFORE LEAVING THE SECULAR WORLD
- Let's get changed.
- Okay.
OFF THEY GO TO GET CHANGED
Wonhee and Miyeon,
you look great in the uniform.
- Thank you.
For our temple stay program,
we'll first take a stroll
to get to know more about the temple.
- Next, we'll have a tea break.
- Sounds good.
We'll make prayer beads through 108 bows
and try meditation as well.
And lastly,
hoping your wishes will come true,
- we'll light a candle for each of you.
- A candle? I see.
How does that plan sound to you?
- Amazing.
- Lovely.
- Are you looking forward to it?
- Yes.
TOUR OF THE TEMPLE
Shall we, then?
- Okay.
- Sure!
We're in the presence of Buddha.
BUDDHA STATUE STANDING GUARD
Press your palms together like this.
This gesture means,
"I respect you with all my heart."
We'll greet Buddha.
NEW FOLLOWERS GREET BUDDHA
FOR THE FIRST TIME
This statue here is Maitreya Buddha.
- Maitreya Buddha.
- That's right.
Maitreya Buddha speaks to us
through his hand gestures.
Can you guess what each gesture means?
- What does this mean?
- Right, you hold it up like this.
His left hand is pointing downward
with his palm showing.
That means, "Tell me what you desire.
I will make your wishes come true."
He's inviting us to share our worries
and wishes with him
- so that he can help us.
- He's offering to help?
Now the right hand.
It means that
since he will look out for us,
we can live confidently and peacefully,
free from concerns.
- In other words, "Don't be afraid."
- Because he'll be there for us?
- That's so nice.
- That's his message.
During the program,
feel free to share your burdens
before Buddha.
Hopefully, when you leave,
you'll be confident, peaceful,
and free of worries.
- Let's make that happen.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Okay.
- Sounds great.
- Shall we go to the Daeungjeon Hall?
- Yes.
So that's what the gestures meant.
OFF TO THE NEXT SITE
- The panel reads "Daeungjeon Hall."
- Yes.
As the name suggests,
this hall is dedicated to the Great Hero.
Let's go inside.
When you visit a shrine
in a Buddhist temple,
you greet Buddha right upon entry.
Turn toward the statue,
press your palms together,
and take a half bow.
After that,
we'll take a full bow
known as the five-point prostration.
Our bodies' 5 points,
including 2 knees, 2 elbows,
and the forehead, should touch the floor.
We pay our respects
in the humblest posture.
- For the bow?
- Yes.
- We all have sharp, thorny impulses.
- Of course.
Greed and anger fall into that category.
As we kneel and bow,
we leave them on the floor.
- "Sharp, thorny impulses."
- Exactly.
Once you let them go,
it'll be like the clouds parting
to reveal the sun.
You'll find clarity in your minds as well.
With that, we'll rise.
When you visit a Buddhist temple,
the common etiquette is
to bow three times.
Shall we, then?
- Let's bow to Buddha three times.
- Sure.
All right. Press your palms together
and take a half bow.
Kneel.
COPY AND PASTE
Next, place your hands on the floor.
Rest your elbows on the floor.
Let your forehead meet the floor.
Turn your hands over
and raise them to your ears.
Now lower them.
LIKE THIS?
There you go.
Press your palms together again.
HALF A BEAT LATE
Push through your feet and stand up.
There we go.
Well done.
Let's take our second bow.
Repeat the process.
RARE SIGHT OF WONHEE BEING SERIOUS
Lastly, because the third bow
is our last one,
we'll lift our forehead a bit
and place our hands underneath.
- Do you have a wish?
- Yes.
Share it with Buddha in your mind.
PLEASE LET THEM COME TRUE
Then we can stand back up.
Now the finish.
SUCCESSFUL FIRST MEETING
After the three bows,
simply rest in Buddha's presence.
All right.
Now that we have greeted Buddha,
- let's go have tea together.
- Okay.
Wow, I'm surprised to see
all these different buildings.
- Please come on in.
- Okay.
Here we are.
This way.
COZY AND QUIET
TEATIME WITH BHIKSHUNI YEOMOK
- Make yourselves at home.
- Okay.
SUPER RESPECTFUL POSE
STARES
Are you comfortable?
- You don't have to kneel.
- Really?
- Of course.
- How should I sit?
- You can just...
- I wanted to be respectful.
Fold the back of the cushion like I did.
- It's so comfy.
- Really?
- Much better?
- Yes.
There we go.
SET FREE
We'll be having five-flavored berry tea.
As its name suggests,
it has all five flavors.
Can you guess them all?
Salty, sweet, sour...
I swear I know them all.
I love five-flavored berries.
- Shall we try it first, then?
- Okay.
Here you go.
Such a pretty color.
Hold your hand like this
and rest your teacup on it.
Think of today's teatime
as your gift for yourself,
the most precious person in the world.
- A gift for myself.
- Yes, that's it.
Hold up your cup,
gaze at it,
and appreciate its aroma.
TEA ETIQUETTE
Taste it.
TAKE A SIP
MHM
It tastes better this way.
All right.
- Have you figured it out?
- Sour, sweet,
- salty, bitter...
- That's right.
What comes next?
I can't recall the last one.
SO ELUSIVE
LAST ANSWER: SPICY
Now that we've had a sip,
let's have a chat.
Feel free to ask me anything.
WONHEE FIRST
Ma'am.
How do you handle stress?
I tend to avoid stressful situations.
What if they're unavoidable?
They're unavoidable?
All right, then.
- I'll have to bear it.
- The stress?
No, the situation itself.
- I'll have to ride it out.
- Ride it out?
Or you can try shifting your focus
away from the stressful situation.
You can leave it behind,
just like you did today.
AS THEY FOUND REFUGE IN THE TEMPLE
Even as your emotions rage like a storm,
take time to understand
what your heart truly wants.
Ask yourself
how you would like to lead your life.
I think moments like that
call for self-reflection.
GAIN A BETTER UNDERSTANDING OF YOURSELF
Take a short nap,
- take a shower,
- That's a good idea.
or clean your room.
Oh, cleaning.
I clean my room daily these days.
- That's a great habit.
- It's therapeutic.
I decorate and clean my room.
- It's my little therapy.
- Really?
Cleaning gives me so much stress.
Can I visit to clean sometime?
- Hit me up anytime.
- Oh, no.
I'D LOVE TO DO THAT
Don't you have any questions, Miyeon?
I lack self-control.
The world is full of amazing...
LET ME DRINK THIS TEA FIRST
...snacks.
Whenever I see them,
I can't control myself.
How do I build self-restraint?
This doesn't apply to appetite alone.
Suppressing your urges
is stressful in general.
- Right?
- Exactly.
As followers of Buddha,
we practice patience.
PATIENCE: SPIRITUAL VIRTUE OF ENDURING
AND BEARING HARDSHIP
But in your case,
you're repressing an urge
that is already there.
You're forcing yourself to behave.
"Don't get mad.
Don't be depressed. Don't be sad."
Do you tend to hold back your anger?
- I don't.
- I do.
As a celebrity,
you have to hold it in, right?
I tend to let it go.
Do you?
You're cool that way.
- She's pretty cool.
- I see.
Those who hold back
may think it'd be satisfying.
Isn't it?
It leaves you with regrets.
After an outburst,
- you're left with regret.
- That's true.
But when you hold it in,
you end up with stress.
What a headache, right?
Could we combine our personalities?
UNIFICATION ATTEMPT
You know, patience isn't
just about denying your urges.
It's about giving yourself time.
Your emotions may surge like a tidal wave,
but don't let them take over.
Instead, take a moment
to think about what you truly want.
Rather than suppressing your urges,
think of it as a chance
to take better care of yourself.
That way, you avoid the stress.
Would I have to think first
when I get angry?
No, you need to stop thinking.
- Stop it?
- Yes.
Don't get caught up in your thoughts.
Take a pause.
Then you'll have the clarity to see
what your heart truly wants.
You can make a decision you won't regret.
What should I do
when I'm worried about the future?
So many participants
share the same concern.
"The world changes so fast.
I'm afraid I can't keep up
with the speed."
It makes them anxious.
If you let your worries take over,
they become a habit.
- Don't let it become a habit.
- Exactly.
WHAT'S UP WITH HER?
Don't let it become--
She's so serious.
Just what is eating you up so much?
CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE
Maybe she's just very curious.
THIS YOUNG FOLLOWER
IS CURIOUS ABOUT EVERYTHING
NOW I KNOW
Don't let it become a habit.
Honestly, it's so nice
that your advice is clear and practical.
Let's practice meditation later.
We'll reflect on our wishes
while making prayer beads
- through 108 bows.
- Okay.
- Why don't we finish the tea?
NOT WASTING A DROP
- Shall we?
- Yes.
PRAYER BEADS THROUGH 108 BOWS
We'll now make prayer beads
through 108 bows.
Have you ever seen prayer beads?
- Yes.
- Yes, as a bracelet.
The prayer beads we're going to make
will help us count
as we practice 108 bows.
The prayer beads literally mean
"beads of the mind."
They're a reminder to keep Buddha
in our hearts and minds.
While that is their main purpose,
they're also helpful
when your mind is on a roller coaster.
In such times,
they can help you find composure.
Counting the beads
will help calm your mind.
First, why don't you open
the plastic bag with the beads?
Now pour them into the bowl.
BEADS TO HELP EMPTY YOUR MIND
All right. Good.
Do you see a string?
Form a knot on one end.
Don't make it too tight, though.
We're only tying up one end
so that the beads don't fall out.
Don't tighten it. Keep it loose.
Good. Next.
I'll recite 108 Bows to Happiness
as you practice bowing.
After reading each item on the list,
I'll strike the bamboo clapper.
You can bow then.
As you come back up,
thread one bead onto the string.
Just one bead.
Then sit like this
with your palms together.
You'll thread 1 bead after 1 bow.
UNDERSTOOD
- That's it.
- I get it.
108-BOW SESSION BEGINS
Press your palms together.
Half bow.
SLIDES DOWN
- Half bow.
- Half bow?
Again.
- Half bow.
- Do a half bow before a full one.
2ND ATTEMPT
A PROPER HALF BOW THIS TIME
"With utmost appreciation
and respect toward all living beings,
we now take a bow."
SNAP
BOWS AT THE SNAP
That's right.
Place your palms on the floor.
Raise your torso and thread one bead.
ONE LESS CONCERN FOR EVERY BEAD
SNAP
On your feet now.
ENDLESS CYCLE OF BOWS BEGINS
"As we humble ourselves
to control our ill tempers,
we now take a bow."
SNAP
The world is full of amazing snacks.
REPENTING OBSESSION WITH FOOD
I can't control myself.
What should I do
when I'm worried about the future?
LETTING GO OF HER FEARS ABOUT THE FUTURE
FUMBLES
THREADS A BEAD IN A FLASH
THEY'RE NOT AT THE SAME SKILL LEVEL
THE EXPERIENCE TURNS
INTO A JOURNEY OF TROUBLES
WHEN WONHEE COMPLETES HER THREADING
MIYEON JUST GETS READY
SNAP
RUSHING
"May we not misunderstand others..."
SCRAMBLING
JUST A SECOND... THAT WAS TOO FAST
MIYEON, SPEED UP
THERE GOES THE BEAD
RUSHING
A TIMING GAME BEGINS
BEATS OF 108-BOW EXPERIENCE
WILL CONFUSE YOU
GATHERS HERSELF TO FOCUS
SNAP
I'M GIVING UP
What on earth?
How are you managing it?
- Take your time and rise.
- Just do it.
I CAN'T, THOUGH
AS FOR WONHEE
SHE NAILS IT EVERY TIME
A SKILLED PRAYER BEADS MAKER
AM I THREADING THE BEADS
OR ARE THE BEADS SOMEHOW THREADING ME?
ONE WITH THE BEADS
PERFECT HARMONY
SOMEWHERE BETWEEN TRAINING AND SUFFERING
THEY LET GO OF THEIR WORRIES AND DESIRES
JUST WHEN THE DOPAMINE RUSH
IS ABOUT TO HIT THEM...
This is our last bow.
FINALLY, THE LAST ONE
"May our 108 wishes come true."
Thread your last bead.
ONE LAST BEAD
TO TAKE THEIR LAST CONCERN AWAY
There. Make sure to tighten the knot.
Tie them together.
WITH A KNOT SECURELY TIED
Fasten the knot.
You have your prayer beads now.
Your 108 worries have become prayer beads
filled with new wishes.
PRAYER BEADS OBTAINED
Thank you.
Let's wrap up with a meditation
to calm our minds.
- What was that?
- A bug.
Oh, no. Killing is forbidden, right?
WHAT DO I DO?
Go on. Set it free.
It's still alive.
Bye.
- It might've survived.
- I'm sure it did.
It just got knocked out.
MEDITATION TIME
Sit up straight.
Straighten your back and sit up properly.
Hold up your right hand
as we did earlier during the teatime.
Place your left hand on top of it.
Make a circle with your thumbs.
Open your chest.
CRACK
Did I hear something?
Not at all.
Did you hear anything?
THEY HAVE EACH OTHER'S BACKS
No.
Close your eyes.
There you go.
Next, take a deep breath in.
Exhale.
Imagine your body
filling up like a balloon.
Focus on controlling our breath.
EYES WIDE OPEN
LOST FOCUS
LOCKING IN AGAIN
FINDING INNER PEACE THROUGH MEDITATION
Shall we end the day with a light snack?
- Yes.
- Great.
THEIR RESTING STOP IS NAMED
"MIND-RESTING GAZEBO"
- Wow, they look so good.
- Right.
I'm hungry.
ELEGANT ASSORTMENT OF REFRESHMENTS
TO EASE THEIR HUNGER
I didn't get a good look at you until now.
We spent the whole day
bowing side by side.
What did you think about
during our meditation?
Nothing.
- Same.
- Really?
Now and then, I took a peek.
I had to focus again
because everyone was deep in meditation.
You said you were hungry.
Bon appétit.
LET ME GET THAT SWEET RICE CAKE
This looks like you.
You know what?
PROTESTING AT THE COMPARISON
- I'm startled.
- Yeah?
Your face isn't that round.
- Right?
- Yeah.
I'M NO LONGER "CIRCLE," OKAY?
Not really, no.
That reminds me.
My show is called Hello, Twenty - Wonhee.
So I ask this to all my guests.
What was your life like at 20?
My life at 20?
To be honest,
10 YEARS AGO
I barely remember.
DIDN'T SEE THAT COMING
- Well...
- I get it.
I wasn't really ready to become an adult.
It was quite sudden.
Back then, I wasn't particularly excited.
I wasn't ready to turn 20 yet.
I had that sense of panic.
MORE AWKWARD THAN EXCITED
TOTALLY FEELING IT
- I get it.
- Was that a response to me
or to the rice cake?
Both, actually.
It was a two-birds-with-one-stone moment.
What was the first thing you tried
when you turned 20?
I just stayed out late.
Minors have to get home early.
But as an adult,
you definitely have more freedom.
You can stay out as late as you want.
You're an adult, after all.
- Because I'm an adult.
- I'm a grown-up.
I hear that you're a total extrovert.
Were you outgoing back in school, too?
- I'm not that outgoing.
- Moderately outgoing?
I was a total introvert back in school.
- I was the opposite.
- Really?
Back in middle school,
I went crazy and became extroverted.
Ever since I was a little,
- I've always been timid.
- Seriously?
Puberty had made me go crazy.
Social skills are everything
in our line of work.
I guess I'm an extrovert by circumstance.
I don't think social skills have
anything to do with being an extrovert.
Everyone is so fixated
on the whole MBTI classification.
I want to build
a good relationship with others,
so I pluck up my courage and do my best.
But they would sometimes accuse me
of not being an introvert.
You were doing your best.
That leaves me speechless.
It must be upsetting
to have your efforts ignored.
I used to enjoy talking
about the MBTI classification.
I used it to break the ice, too.
But nowadays,
the whole thing wears me out.
I get it. Not all extroverts are the same.
- Exactly.
- So much generalization.
Are you shy around strangers?
I like people in general,
but I'm still shy around strangers.
I'm the same way,
but I can mask what I'm feeling.
That's cool. How did you learn to do that?
The pressure I get
on variety shows helped.
Wonhee, you're something else.
ME?
Basically, you overcame
this obstacle on your own.
- Even though you're an introvert--
- I didn't overcome anything.
- I respond well to training.
- So you think you were born that way?
I guess I'm pretty adaptable.
- I think I am.
- Really?
The more I get to know you,
the more mysterious you seem.
You're an enigma.
Thank you.
Did you just thank me?
It's nice, though.
It simply means
you're a multifaceted person.
Thank you.
OUT OF HABIT
Why do you keep thanking me?
You look like a quokka when you smile.
So cute.
QUOKKA MIYEON
You said you were shy around strangers.
Do you tend to open up right away,
or does it take time for you to do that?
I usually like people right away.
AMAZED
But it takes me a while to make a friend.
What about you?
I like people in general,
but I have high standards
when it comes to friends.
There are only a few people
who meet the standards.
Tell me, Wonhee.
How many close friends do you have?
- Just 1.
- Just 1?
You must have insanely high standards.
I'm close with my group, obviously.
But apart from them,
I only have one close friend.
HOW FASCINATING
Really?
Say you're exhausted from a busy schedule.
What do you do to cheer yourself up?
I've come to realize
that you need stamina to enjoy anything.
Even something exciting isn't fun
when you're exhausted.
- You can't really focus, right?
- Of course.
I always make an effort to stay healthy.
I never skip meals.
- Meals?
- Yes.
I take supplements on a regular basis.
At the end of the day,
we live pretty irregular lives.
- Yeah.
- So I rest
EVEN ON A BRIEF BREAK
whenever I get the chance.
MIYEON MAKES AN EFFORT TO RECHARGE
I make sure to get plenty of rest.
That is the best we can do.
When do you unwind and recharge?
Being out helps me recharge.
- I'm feeling it now, actually.
- Really?
- Frankly--
- I have to be in my dorm.
When I'm in my room, cleaning,
lying in bed, or sitting at my desk...
- That's when I relax.
- Seriously?
Wait.
Did you ask me that
just so you could say all that?
SAW RIGHT THROUGH HER
I just don't get it.
How do you relax
when you're out and about?
- I'm doing fine now.
- It's just...
- Really?
- I mean it.
- I'm happy to hear it.
- When I'm home,
I keep thinking about tomorrow.
You know that "me time" at home?
I'm not very good at spending time alone.
When I'm out and surrounded by people,
I feel more at ease.
That's what sets introverts
and extroverts apart.
I suppose so.
What goes through your mind
when you need to psych yourself up?
I don't think all that much.
So you don't overthink
or let your imagination run wild?
What's the point of overthinking?
I WANT TO BE LIKE YOU
How admirable.
I think about all sorts of stuff.
Like what to eat later?
Sort of.
Weirdly, I don't crave food
when I'm on a diet.
- Don't lose weight.
- Why not?
- You're cute as you are now.
- Oh, come on.
- You look good now. Don't lose weight.
- Come on.
Isn't it unfair when skinny, hot girlies
tell me not to lose weight?
- I feel--
- Not me.
Look, I'm eating nonstop.
Heard of Changeok Rice Cake?
Yeah, but I've never tried it.
I have some in my van.
I've already had one,
and the rest is also mine.
Nothing for me?
That's so mean.
- Aren't you jealous?
- I'll get some myself later.
It's fabulous.
The sponge cake crumbs
on the rice cake fall off easily,
so you need to be careful.
What's your favorite food?
A snack like this?
Yeah, I enjoy nibbling on light snacks.
I love ramyeon, too.
Ramyeon is amazing.
- I love baked goods and rice cakes.
- Really?
- It must be hard watching what you eat.
- It's a nightmare.
If I have a snack,
I know I'll have to skip a meal.
Snacks never fill me up,
but I still can't stop eating them.
And the cycle repeats.
You sure think a lot.
HABITUAL OVERTHINKER
Do you like working out?
- Not really, right?
- No.
But I've recently started ballet.
- It suits you.
- Here's the thing.
People always laugh when I mention it,
so I usually don't.
- But it's perfect for you.
- I've just picked it up.
Are you flexible?
I am on the flexible side.
- I'm not, so I don't like ballet.
- Really?
My splits are horrible.
I could never have guessed.
- Wonhee, I think...
- Yes?
- You livestream sometimes
- Right.
about cosmetics.
- You're a huge makeup geek.
- I am.
I've bought some items you recommended.
SO HAPPY
Really? That's an honor.
You show which products look better
when mixed together.
VERY PROUD
After watching a few clips,
your videos kept appearing on my feed.
I got hooked and bought a few items
from your videos.
VERY HONORED
You're famous
for being a spectacular beauty.
No, I'm not.
I'm over that phase now.
- How come?
- It was all for a bit.
Are there moments when you think,
"Jeez, I look stunning"?
After I get my hair and makeup done.
The moment I look in the mirror,
I feel like a whole new person.
I know what you mean.
- I also get shocked.
- You do?
"How did this happen?"
- I'm sure you look the same.
- Oh, no.
The makeup artists practically sculpt me
a new nose every time.
I'm like, "Huh?"
Sometimes, I even feel guilty
because I look so different.
What? No way.
I really feel guilty.
You must know full well
that you're super cute.
I have that youthful look,
and I'm not fully satisfied with it.
I'm not cutesy and sweet,
personality-wise.
So it feels like false advertising.
- I mean, I'm not all that cute.
- Look.
But everyone tells me I am.
And that's a compliment.
Deep down,
I know that and enjoy hearing it.
That really gives me the ick.
That's exactly what I go through.
- Me too.
- You feel me, right?
When I review my work
and catch myself acting cute,
- I feel like puking.
- I get it.
Now that I think about it,
you're not the soft type.
You look like a cute little angel,
but you're actually laid-back.
Even calling myself laid-back
- gives me the ick.
- Yeah?
- It's just funny. Don't you agree?
- I get it.
- You were just born with a cute face
- I'm not all that chill.
- and a chill soul.
- I'm not chill.
I can hold a grudge.
When someone asks,
"You know you're cute, right?"
I'm lost.
Even if I deny that,
they're like, "Yeah, right."
It's a nightmare.
See? That's how I got caught up
in the princess mess.
But I can't even say,
"Yes, I'm very cute."
- You feel me, right?
- Of course.
A queen like you should get it.
- I get where you're coming from.
- Right?
PRINCESS MIYEON'S DEFENSE
I never thought I was that pretty.
But my team always does their best
to glam me up.
Objectively speaking, I'm not bad-looking.
- You're stunning.
- So basically--
You're downright beautiful.
Accept it, okay?
You're cute. Accept that, too.
Anyway, it doesn't feel right
to reject their compliments.
When you deny a compliment,
things get awkward, right?
While thanking people
for their kind words,
I somehow ended up creating
this princess persona.
At first, I just thanked them.
Then I started adding, "Yeah, I'm pretty."
And gradually,
I got too committed to the bit.
I see.
The whole bit took hold of me.
I kept rolling with it for a while.
But that's not who I really am.
- Right?
- Did it ever become a burden?
Well, I wasn't affected that much.
- You really got into character.
- I guess so.
It didn't really bother me.
I made all those silly comments as a joke.
But even my mom asked me this.
"You don't honestly believe
what you're saying, right?"
People around me
actually started worrying.
I realized it was time...
- To dial things down?
- Yes.
I decided it was time
to leave that phase behind.
So can you switch personas on and off?
You make it look so easy.
"Yep, I'm pretty. Bye!"
- You then turn it off.
- I can do that.
When you need it, you turn it back on.
I can do that at will because I like both.
HAS HIGH SELF-ESTEEM
Both are great.
Lately, I've been questioning that.
You and your group, i-dle,
have been working together
for a long time.
You've renewed your contracts
several times.
What's the secret
to staying together for so long?
Honestly, arguing helps.
That's how we are.
We never argue.
You never argue?
Do you always understand each other?
It works for my group
because everyone is
easygoing and kindhearted.
So not a single one of you
is confrontational?
Not really, no.
No matter how close you get
with your members,
you can never fully understand them.
I believe everyone thinks
and expresses themselves differently.
Even if you think
you're being considerate,
it can still lead to frustration
if you don't communicate clearly.
Idols have to spend a long time
- with their members.
- Right.
For us, talking things through
whenever we had a conflict really helped.
When I ask veteran idols
for their secret to good teamwork,
everyone tells me, "Fight a lot."
Of course, it doesn't have to be physical.
NOTED
This is the final segment of my show.
- Already?
- We've reached that point.
I always ask this question
to all my guests.
Could you give me advice on turning 20?
- Advice?
- Yes.
I'd appreciate it.
First of all,
congratulations on turning 20.
I mean, it's a beautiful age.
You must've worked long and hard
preparing for your debut.
Now that you have turned 20,
I hope you make
plenty of time for yourself
and try everything
you've always wanted to do
in that golden year.
- Thank you.
- I should thank you.
I really appreciate it.
- Do you feel rested now?
- Yes.
Great.
At first, I simply thought
I had two pretty participants.
Over the course of the program,
I discovered that you're beautiful
inside and out.
It made me want to root for both of you.
Here are the wish candles.
Write down your name and wish.
- Thank you.
- My name?
My name is...
MY FAMILY'S HAPPINESS AND WELL-BEING
...FOR MANY YEARS TO COME
WISH CANDLES READY
What did you put?
I put, "My family's happiness
and well-being."
That's what I wrote.
Was I being too selfish?
- Don't worry about it.
- I wrote,
"May I stay healthy and cheerful
so I can continue to work
for many years to come."
Work never even crossed my mind.
OFF THEY GO WITH THEIR WISH CANDLES
Oh, I'm full.
- No trouble writing your wishes?
- None.
Light your candle
and place it inside the case.
WITH HER WHOLE HEART
WONHEE'S CANDLE IS ALL SET
MIYEON'S CANDLE IS ALSO ALL SET
There.
THEY TAKE A HALF BOW,
HOPING THEIR WISHES WILL COME TRUE
"BE KIND TO YOURSELF
AND MAKE THE MOST OF THE PRECIOUS TIME"
So many cute items.
That's so cute.
RIGHT UP WONHEE'S ALLEY
This is so pretty. I dig it.
GOAL: FIGURE OUT WONHEE'S TASTE
EPISODE 7 GIRLIE
CHARLES
IN SEARCH OF TASTE WITH THE GIRLIE'S HELP
- I've already picked one out.
- Show me.
This one.
HER TASTE WILL SHOCK YOU
Isn't it cute?
How's this? It caught my eye right away.
WONHEE'S TASTE IS JUST AS SHOCKING
What about this? It's pretty cute.
THIS GIRLIE HAS HER STANDARDS
THE GAP BETWEEN THEM WIDENS
I thought I was so savvy and cunning.
I don't think that way.
Whoever texts me is a flirt.
FACED WITH ENDLESS DIFFERENCES
WILL WONHEE FIND HER TASTE?
Subtitle translation by Jeongwoo Kim